Did you have any contact with Count Mazuurek after that?
その後　マズゥールカ卿との連絡は？
No.
いえ　しかし揚陸城はまだ生きています
However, his Landing Castle is still operational.
If the Aldnoah Drive in it remains active,
then he must still be alive.
アルドノアが動いているということは
マズゥールカ卿も生きているということ
隙を伺って身を潜めているか　もしくは…
Perhaps he hides to wait for a better opportunity.
The alternative is...
地球人に捕らえられたか
That he was taken prisoner by the Terrans.
どちらにせよ　マズゥールカ卿の帰還は絶望的
Either way, it would be prudent
to assume he will not return soon.
となると　すべきことは一つ
In which case, our hands are tied.
貴公　一体何を
What do you imply?
We must muzzle the Terran stray.
これ以上地球生まれの野良犬を　野放しにはできません
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
君の手が広げた　何もない空よ
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
理屈の海だけの　解を遊べば
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
ほどいては溢れた　お互いのナミダ
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
降下した言葉・嘘・キマグレ
soul art
Soul art
soul・art　リズムを奏でて
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
合図をリングに繋ぐ
形だけのシステムと
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
形見だけの呪いも
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
逃亡人の恥じらい音
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
想像Drive　CarryOn　意地なTIRE
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
誤解あるドアに　ゼロが眠りかけた
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
時計抱いた人と天使
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
永久に飽くドール達
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
また同じ風邪に　モガいて
No anomalies during supply and maintenance.
補給および点検は予定通り　遅れはありません
All is proceeding to schedule.
艦載機の修理は　基地の整備工場と連携して遅れを取り戻しています
We are working with the base's maintenance depot to repair our units in a more timely manner.
Very good.
よろしい　作業を継続してください
Carry on.
Yes, ma'am.
はい
What of our Martian prisoner?
例の火星騎士は？
Not a word.
何も　寡黙な殿方のようですね
It seems he's the silent type.
Mizusaki, do you know why men of the silent type are popular?
不見咲君　寡黙な殿方がなぜモテるか知っていますか
落ち着いて見えるからでしょうか
Because they seem at ease?
Because they shut up and listen to you.
黙って話を聞いてくれるからです
And the reinforcements?
人員の補充は？
Y-Yes, ma'am.
は…はい
すでに完了し　各部署のシフトも調整済みです
They're aboard, and their shifts have been set up.
A few are old acquaintances.
前のクルーも何名か入っています
For instance, Warrant Officer Kaizuka
and Lieutenant Marito.
界塚准尉　鞠戸大尉
Dr. Yagarai is also back and serving as a medical officer with the rank of second lieutenant.
合わせて耶賀頼先生が少尉に　正式に軍医として着任しました
それと　界塚少尉より　火星騎士尋問の申請が来ています
Also, Second Lieutenant Kaizuka requests to interrogate the Mars Knight.
The younger brother?
弟君が？
アナリティカル・エンジンを使用したいとのことです
He says he'd like to use his analytical engine.
これ　伊奈帆君が自分でプログラムしたのかい
Did you write the software yourself?
I just customized the firmware it was already running.
もともとあったファームをカスタマイズしただけです
The interface area has expanded too.
領域も拡張されている
気分は？
How do you feel?
Not much different.
特に変わりは
これ以上は広げないようにね
Try not to let it get any larger.
By the time you notice it affecting your brain, it'll be too late.
脳が影響を受けてからじゃ遅いよ
I won't.
はい　危険は理解してますから
I'm aware of the risks.
Hey, Nao.
なお君　ここにいたの
Yuki.
ユキ姉
Can I talk to you?
ちょっといい
Why did you decide to serve aboard this ship, Nao?
なお君　どうしてこの船に乗ったの
What are you getting at?
どうしてって
あなたは　わざわざ戦う必要なんてないでしょう
There's no reason you have to fight.
You should have gone back to your old life after the hospital stay.
怪我は治ったら　そのまま避難するべきなのに
それはユキ姉だって同じでしょう
That goes for you too, then.
No, it doesn't!
同じじゃないわ
I'm a soldier!
私は軍人よ
そもそも軍人になる必要なんてなかったんだから　同じだよ
But there was no reason you had to join the army in the first place. Same thing.
No, it isn't!
違うわ
Do you know how much it torments me
that I turned you into a soldier?
私　後悔してるの　あなた軍人にしてしまったことを
あの時血まみれで倒れているあなたを見て
When I saw you that day, lying in a pool of blood,
I kept asking myself why I hadn't stopped you.
なんであなたのこと止めなかったんだろうって
私はね　あなたと　あなたの住む世界を守りたくて軍人になったの
I became a soldier because I wanted to protect you and the world you live in.
And look at us now.
それなのに…
ごめん
I'm sorry.
でも　じっとしてられないんだ
But I can't just sit back and watch.
Because of the princess?
やっぱりあのお姫様？
あの人はもう　あなたの知っているアセイラム姫じゃないわ
That girl isn't the Princess Asseylum you used to know.
地球を侵略する敵になったのよ
She's hellbent on conquering the Earth. That makes her the enemy.
That one's an impostor.
あれは偽物だよ　本物はどこかで生きている
The real one is still alive somewhere.
How can you possibly know that?!
どうしてそんなことが分かるの
Because that is the evaluation of my left eye.
僕の左目がそう分析した
In light of the circumstances,
she's probably confined somewhere.
状況から鑑みて　きっと自由な環境ではないと思う
だから　僕はセラムさんを助けたい
That's why I want to rescue Seylum.
That's absurd!
そんなの無理よ
Yuki, they shot her right in front of me.
ユキ姉　彼女は僕の目の前で撃たれたんだ
She tried to help me when I was wounded.
負傷した僕を助けようとして　撃たれたんだ
And they shot her.
だから　僕が助けなきゃ
That's why I have to rescue her.
Nao!
なお君
It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
How's your Cataphract?
機体の状態は？
診断にかけたら　重力波でサブフレームに歪みが来ちまってて
The grease monkeys ran some tests, and even the sub-frame is warped.
It needs a complete overhaul.
ほとんどオーバーホールですかね
お酒をやめたと伺いました
I hear you quit drinking.
My doctor wouldn't get off my back.
口うるさい主治医がいるもんで
では　祝杯も挙げられませんね
I guess a toast wouldn't be appropriate, then.
Toasts don't count.
祝杯は別腹です
Do you ever stick to anything?
あなたという人は
Doctor's orders.
主治医に飲まされたんです　薬ですよ
It's medicinal.
気分はいかがですか
How do you feel?
You don't look too well.
あまりよくないようですね
身体検査を受けたと聞きました
I'm told you were subjected to a full cavity search.
まさか　ここまで原始的な調べ方だとは思わなかった
I expected a primitive interrogation, but that took the cake.
奥歯に仕込んだ毒を使われては困りますから
We can't have you killing yourself with a cyanide-laden tooth.
時代錯誤な
How antiquated.
Yes, I feel that describes your nation quite well.
そのようなお国柄と伺っています
I suppose the feudal system in Vers
must seem bizarrely outdated to a Terran.
地球人からすれば　ヴァースの封建制度など時代遅れも甚だしいだろう
問題があるなら　自分たちで変えればいい
If you don't like it, do something about it.
Only one born into a land of plenty would say that.
満ち足りた地に生まれた者らしい
まるで死にかけの豚だ
You're like pigs walking into an abattoir.
冷えて身動き取れなくなってからでは遅いぞ
Once you see the butcher's knife, it's too late.
よく知ってますね
You know a fair bit.
認めるのか
You admit I'm right?
いえ　豚のことです
I mean you know a fair bit about pigs.
アセイラム姫は鳥も見たことがなかったのに
Princess Asseylum hadn't seen birds,
but knew of them.
アセイラム姫と話したことがあるのか
You spoke with Princess Asseylum?
この船に乗っていました
She spent time aboard this ship.
そうか
I see.
姫を利用する者の一人か
You are one of those who sought to exploit her, then.
利用ではありません　協力です
There was no exploitation.
It was cooperation.
Cooperation?
協力だと？
一つ教えてもらえますか
Could you tell me something?
私が国を売るほど安い男に見えるとでも？
Do I look like someone who would betray his country?
見えませんね　聞こえもしません
Your voice and mannerisms do not suggest so.
なおさら好都合です
Which makes you the perfect man to ask.
あなたはアセイラム姫に　忠誠を誓っていますか
Are you loyal to Princess Asseylum?
ライエちゃん　食べないの
Aren't you eating, Rayet?
You can't go to battle on an empty stomach, you know.
少しは食べないと　出撃の時持たないよ
食欲なくて
I'm not hungry.
If you starve yourself on a diet,
your boobs are the first thing to go.
食べないダイエットは胸から落ちるよ
I've never been on a diet.
したことないわよ　ダイエットなんて
ライエちゃん　ダイエットしたことないの
You've never been on a diet? Not once?
That's amazing!
すごい　どうやってスタイル維持してるの
How do you stay so slim?
私にも教えてもらえますか
I'd like to know too.
Ma'am!
副長
お食事ですか
Here for lunch?
寄港した時ぐらい　船の外で食べようかと思いまして
I thought I might as well eat somewhere
besides the ship's mess while we're docked.
Yeah, we don't get that chance very often.
外食なかなかできないですもんね
That reminds me!
そういえば　伊奈帆見ませんでしたか
Anybody seen Inaho?
I wanted to ask him to join us, but he was just gone.
お昼誘おうと思ったのに見つからなくて
Second Lieutenant Kaizuka is interrogating the Mars Knight right now.
界塚少尉なら　今火星兵の尋問をしてるところです
えっ　伊奈帆がですか
Inaho is?
I'm going back to the ship.
先戻ってる
ちょっと　ライエ
Wait!
Rayet?
She didn't tell us how she does it.
スタイルの話を…
では君は…
So you're saying that the Princess Asseylum currently at the moon base is an impostor?
今現在月面基地におられるアセイラム姫殿下が　偽物だというのか
はい
Yes.
だとすれば　本物のアセイラム姫は今どこに
If that is true, then where is the real one?
どこかに捕らえられているのか
Is she being held prisoner somewhere?
それとも表に出られぬ理由があるのか
Or is there a reason she can't show herself?
Perhaps both.
あるいはその両方
Is that what your left eye told you?
それもその左目で見抜いたと？
It's called an analytical engine.
アナリティカル・エンジンです
バカな
Laughable!
そのような戯れ言を信じるほど　このマズゥールカ愚かではないわ
You must think me foolish indeed to have concocted such a preposterous tale.
あなたのカタフラクトを回収しました
We've retrieved your Cataphract.
アルドノアドライブは爆発の衝撃で停止した
Its Aldnoah Drive was knocked offline by the force of the explosion.
It'll never operate again.
もはや再び動かすことはできない
You deactivated it yourself, didn't you?
あなたが停止させたんですよね　地球人に奪われることを恐れて
I assume you feared we would capture it intact.
Weren't you listening?
言っただろう　爆発で機能が停止した
It stopped working after the explosion.
Really?
そうですか　やっぱりあなたが意図して停止させたんですね
No, you definitely deactivated it voluntarily.
もう一度言います
I'll say it once again:
アセイラム姫は偽物です
Princess Asseylum is an impostor.
There are many different species of birds.
鳥にも　いろいろな種類がいます
大きな鳥
Large birds.
小さな鳥
Small birds.
Brilliantly colored birds.
そして　色鮮やか鳥
きれい
They're so beautiful!
鳥はこんなふうに　地球の空を飛ぶんです
This is how they look when they soar through Earth's skies.
Most birds can fly, but some species are flightless.
ほとんどの鳥は空を飛びますが
中には空を飛べない鳥類もいる
飛べない鳥？
Flightless birds?
アセイラム姫はきっと
I think Princess Asseylum would pity the
poor birds that have wings but cannot fly.
翼があるのに飛べないなんて可哀想だと言うかもしれませんね
姫様は　お優しい方ですから
She cares for all, great and small.
However, their inability to fly
does not trouble them in the least.
でも　彼らは飛べなくても平気なんです
むしろ飛べるのに籠で飼われているほうが可哀想かもしれない
I think the truly pitiable birds are those that can fly but are confined to cages.
どうして閉じ込めるのですか
Why would anyone confine them?
それは…
Because...
とても美しいからです
they are so very beautiful.
アセイラム姫は　僕の目の前で撃たれました
Princess Asseylum was shot before my very eyes.
ザーツバルム伯爵の手によって
And Count Saazbaum pulled the trigger.
Impossible!
まさか
そしてスレイン・トロイヤードとともに
He then made his escape with
Slaine Troyard and the dying princess.
瀕死のアセイラム姫を連れ去ったんです
ザーツバルム卿は　アセイラム姫を救い出した英雄だとばかり
We celebrated him as the hero who rescued her!
あいつは英雄なんかじゃない
He's no hero.
あいつはアセイラム姫暗殺計画の首謀者
He was the mastermind behind the plot to assassinate her.
ザーツバルム卿が…
Count Saazbaum?!
They took everything from my father, and then some.
あいつらは父を騙して利用するだけ利用して
虫けらみたいに殺した
Only to crush him like a bug underfoot.
お前　ヴァースの生まれなのか
Are you Vers-born?
そうか
I see.
どの道お前の父親は遅かれ早かれ死んでいた
In any event, your father would have died sooner or later.
逆賊として吊るし上げられなかっただけましだと思ったほうがいい
Just be thankful he wasn't branded a traitor and made an example of.
どういう意味
What?!
You saying my father just had it coming?
父は殺されて当然だったというの
We're done here.
もう行こう
私はまだ
I'm not!
You are.
いいから
Let go of me!
放して
バカだって思ってるでしょう
I know you think I'm stupid.
何時までも過去を引きずって　何時までも囚われて
That I'll always be living in the past.
Never breaking free.
そうよ　私だって同じ
Not like it isn't true. I'm the same as them.
誰かのせいにして　恨んで　妬んで　戦うことしかできない
All I can do is blame others.
Envy them.
Hate them.
Kill them!
バカな火星人
I'm a stupid Martian.
君は違う
You're different.
違わない
I am not.
You are.
違う
I am not.
違わない
You are.
違う
I am not!
違わない
火星人なんて嫌い
I hate Martians!
私は私が大嫌い
Myself... most of all.
マリルシャン伯爵が？
Count Marylcian, you say?
Yes. He has been been hailing us doggedly, insisting to speak to Princess Asseylum.
はい　どうしてもアセイラム姫取り次いで欲しいと
しつこく通信を
スレイン様はなんと
And Sir Slaine?
He is nowhere to be found.
それが　お姿が見つからず
What's the matter?
何の騒ぎです？
下がれ
You may go.
Sir!
はっ
あら　私がいては話もできませんの
Oh? You can't talk with little old me around?
My apologies.
恐れながら
Few know of your existence, even here on the moon base.
レムリナ様の存在を知る者は
この月面基地でも限られております
あまりこのような場所へは
I must ask that you avoid public areas.
Shall I speak to him?
私が話しましょうか
マリルシャンでしょう
It's Count Marylcian, right?
しかし…
But...
何か問題でも
Would that be a problem?
通信を玉座の間へ
Please put him through to the throne room.
アセイラム姫様におかれましては　ご機嫌うるわしゅ
You are too kind, Your Highness.
Please forgive the sudden disturbance.
突然の無礼を　お許しください
ご機嫌よ　マリルシャン伯爵
Good day, Count Marylcian.
それで　この度はどのようなお話でしょう
Now, to what do I owe the pleasure?
トロイヤード卿の許可を得ずの通信
It must be urgent indeed for you to insist on talking to me without going through Count Troyard first.
よほど火急のようですね
いやいや　やはり御身だけとは参りませんか
Goodness. One cannot simply speak to you in confidence?
しかし　見張りをつけるとは
Count Troyard must be quite paranoid to keep you under lock and key thus.
トロイヤード卿はなかなかに過保護でいらっしゃる
My apologies. "Lock and key" was going too far.
見張りは語弊がありますかな
Let us call him a knight, protecting the princess secluded in her ivory tower.
差し詰め　塔に閉じ込められた姫を守るナイトと言った所か
おっと　これはご無礼を申し上げました
Oh! A thousand pardons.
I spoke as if Your Highness were a bird in a cage.
姫殿下を籠の鳥のように
A bird in a cage?
籠の鳥？
地球では自由を奪われた者のことをそのように形容するそうです
I'm told it is a Terran phrase that refers to one deprived of freedom.
Incoming from HQ!
基地本部から入電
The prisoner has escaped!
捕虜が逃走したとの報告です
Put the ship on alert! Update everyone on the double!
全鑑警戒　各所通達急げ
Roger!
了解
もう　勘弁してよね　夜中の警報 と
Can't we go one night without an alarm?
Rayet?
ライエ　早く出動しないと
We gotta get out of...
Rayet?
ライエ
お前か
So it's you.
来て
Come with me.
急いで
Hurry.
どうしてこんなことを
Why are you doing this?
あなたには揚陸城に戻って
I want you to return to your Landing Castle and search for the real Princess Asseylum.
本物のアセイラム姫の居場所を探って欲しいんです
なぜ私に
Why me?
Because you are of the same mind as her.
あなたの志がアセイラム姫と同じだからです
I don't believe you ever had any desire to attack Earth.
元々あなたは地球に攻撃なんかしたくなかったはずだ
それも左目で？
Your left eye again?
Even my right eye was enough for that one.
このぐらい　左目を使わなくてもわかります
あなたは地球のことをよく知っていた
You seem to know a lot about Earth.
A lot more than someone who
saw it only as a target to invade.
侵略地として以上に　地球に興味があるんだ
何でも見通しか
Two all-seeing eyes, huh?
もう一つ　調べて欲しいことが
There's one other thing I'd like you to find out:
スレイン・トロイヤードの目的です
Slaine Troyard's objective.
ここから北に進めば　火星の揚陸城です
Your Landing Castle is directly to the north of here.
You'll need to walk the rest of the way.
あとは歩いてください
Understood.
はい
Catch.
水と食料
Water and food.
逃げきる前に干からびて死なれたら困るから
We can't have you passing out before you get away.
私は死んでもらっても構わないけど
Though personally, I don't care if you live or die.
あなたにはいざという時
If worst comes to worst,
I'll need you to keep Princess Asseylum safe.
アセイラム姫を守ってもらわなければいけない
最後にひとつ　聞いても構わないだろか
One last thing, if you please.
君の名前だ
We haven't introduced ourselves.
I am Mazuurek, proud member of the Vers Orbital Knights' Thirty-Seven Clans.
私はヴァース帝国軌道騎士37家門のひとり　マズゥールカ
マズゥールカ
Mazuurek...
地球に似た名前の民族音楽があります
We have a type of folk music with a similar name.
Indeed. The more I learned of Earth, the more interested I became.
この名の意味を調べるうち
私は地球に深く興味を抱くようになった
君の名は
And your name?
Inaho.
伊奈帆
界塚伊奈帆
Kaizuka Inaho.
Well met, Mazuurek.
マズゥールカさん　アセイラム姫を頼みます
I leave Princess Asseylum in your hands.
承知した
Very well.
界塚伊奈帆
Kaizuka Inaho.
ねえ　どうして私に頼んだの
Tell me.
Why'd you ask me to help with this?
What do you mean, why?
どうしてって
私があの火星人を殺すとは思わなかったの
Did it ever cross your mind I might kill him?
アセイラム姫の時みたいに
Like how I attacked Princess Asseylum.
あの時だって　君は結局殺さなかった
But you didn't kill her.
Not for lack of trying.
殺せなかったのよ
違う
You're wrong.
I'm not.
違わない
You are.
違う
Shut up. I—
しつこいわね　私は…
You are.
違う
君はもう　あの時とは違う
You're not the same person you were back then.
マスタングリーダーよりマスタング11
Mustang Leader to Mustang 11.
What's your status?
そちらの状況は？
マスタング11　異常なし
This is Mustang 11. Nothing to report.
警戒を続けて
Stay on alert.
了解
Roger.
Inaho...
伊奈帆　どうして…
Why?
どういう事だ
What is the meaning of this?
Who gave the Landing Castles permission to dock?
揚陸城の入港など　一体誰が許可した
それが…
Well...
私が許可しました
I did.
Your Highness?
姫
Count Marylcian requested a personal audience with Princess Asseylum.
マリルシャン伯爵はアセイラム姫に直接謁見したいと願っていました
So I granted it.
ですから　許可したのです
私がアセイラム姫…
As Princess Asseylum—no, as a princess of Vers.
いえ
ヴァースの皇女として
なぜ　そのようなことを
Why would you do that?
Let's be off.
行きましょう
客人を待たせるのはマナー違反です
It would be poor manners
to keep our visitors waiting.
アセイラム姫におかれましては　このような突然の謁見をお許しいいただき
We are both humbled and delighted to be granted an audience with Your Highness on such short notice.
恐悦至極に存じます
Count Marylcian.
マリルシャン伯爵　バルークルス伯爵には
Count Barouhcruz.
軌道上の守りを固めていただき　大変感謝しています
You both have my thanks for
bolstering our orbital defenses.
本来なら　地球に降りて領地を広げたい所でありましょう
I understand you would rather be on Earth,
expanding your territory.
We shall leave the conquest of Earth
in the capable hands of our brethren.
地球の占領は私と志同じくする者に任せております
There is no need to worry.
ご心配には及びません
そう　それは良かった
I see. Fortuitous news.
それよりも　アセイラム姫に折り入ってお話がございます
However, we have a matter of
even greater import to discuss.
In light of Count Saazbaum's passing,
先代　ザーツバルム伯爵亡き後
who will inherit the post of royal guard, charged with keeping Your Highness and the moon base safe?
月面基地とアセイラム姫殿下をお守りする近衛兵の任についてでございます
You need not concern yourselves.
その件については　心配には及びません
I have already assumed that role.
私が滞りなく引き継いでおります
アセイラム姫
Princess Asseylum.
殿下のお側にお仕えする栄誉
I would ask for the honor of serving at your side, if it so pleases you.
私に授けていただけないとお願いに参りました
しかし　マリルシャン伯爵
However, Count Marylcian—
I'll thank you to keep your comments to yourself,
口を挟まないでいただきましょうか
Terran!
地球人
This fortress is a bastion of the Vers Empire.
ここはヴァース帝国の御旗を掲げる砦
While I would grudgingly concede to one such as the late Count Saazbaum, Her Highness' savior,
姫殿下救出の功労者たる先代ザーツバルム伯爵が任を賜るなら
遺憾ながらも容認しましょう
しかし　養子とはいえ
did you think I would allow a lowly Terran to assume the role amidst the turmoil of war, son or nay?
地球生まれの貴公がどさくさに紛れ　その任を引き継げるとでも
誇り高き　ヴァース王族の住まわる城に
It is an affront for a mongrel such as yourself to even set foot within this royal sanctuary.
卑しき血筋の者が足を踏み入れること自体　許されぬ所業
What hubris led you to proclaim yourself count when you lack even a Castle of your own?
揚陸城も持たぬ者が伯爵を名乗るのは筋違い
貴公にここを守る資格など　ハナからありません
You have no right to guard this place. You never did.
なら　どうするのです
And what remedy would you suggest?
私のハーシェルと貴公のタルシス
We will pit my Herschel against your Tharsis
どちらが姫を守るのに相応しいか
to determine which of us is worthy of being Her Highness' guard.
明らかにしましょう
私は今この場でトロイヤード伯爵に決闘を申し込む
I challenge you to a duel, Count Troyard!
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
日听:ikiko&Archer   翻译:mam&郝郝
校对:安少&zwx   时间轴:FoH2O   压制:河蟹
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
僕たちは　彷徨える未来
窮屈な空に　ヒカリを探している
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
震える手は無力で
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
叫びはまだ遠くて
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
たけど飛ぶことを恐れてはいられない
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
永遠じゃなくても　完璧じゃなくても
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
背中合わせの世界を　真っ直ぐ生きてゆく
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
何度傷ついても　何度間違えても
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
運命さえ飛び越えていこう
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
この宙の果てまで
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life
創造を信じて